{
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "prompt": "What special prop should always be included for lists of elements?",
      "answers": [
        "id",
        "name",
        "key",
        "prop"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "prompt": "A React component is a function that returns ______.",
      "answers": [
        "HTML",
        "JSX",
        "props",
        "state"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "prompt": "Which event handler will run when a user is finished filling out a form?",
      "answers": [
        "onSubmit",
        "onClick",
        "onChange",
        "onForm"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "prompt": "______ is a tool that transpiles JSX into valid JavaScript.",
      "answers": [
        "React",
        "Babel",
        "Webpack",
        "ES6"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "prompt": "What syntax makes it possible to unpack values from arrays, or properties from objects, into distinct variables?",
      "answers": [
        "spread",
        "key-value",
        "coalescing",
        "destructuring"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 3
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "prompt": "Returning different elements from a component depending on the state of your application is known as _____ rendering.",
      "answers": [
        "voodoo",
        "conditional",
        "reactive",
        "controlled"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Select Answer 4 or you'll get this wrong.",
      "answers": [
        "The loneliest number.",
        "The loneliest number++",
        "Or did I? (I did - don't listen to me.)",
        "I lied - select Answer 3."
      ],
      "correctIndex": "1",
      "id": 7
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Are you sure the new question form is working?",
      "answers": [
        "Pretty sure",
        "Kinda?",
        "Mostly",
        "Definitely"
      ],
      "correctIndex": "2",
      "id": 8
    },
    {
      "prompt": "This is a test",
      "answers": [
        "Test1",
        "Test2",
        "Test3",
        "Test4"
      ],
      "correctIndex": "2",
      "id": 9
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Testing again",
      "answers": [
        "this is the first one",
        "this is the second one",
        "this is the third one",
        "correct answer here"
      ],
      "correctIndex": "1",
      "id": 10
    }
  ]
}